There's gotta be another way out
I've been stuck in a cage with my doubt
I've tried forever getting out on my own.
But every time I do this my way
I get caught in the lies of the enemy
I lay my troubles down
I'm ready for you now.
Bring me out
come and find me in the dark now
Everyday by myself I'm breaking down
I don't wanna fight alone anymore
Bring me out
from the prison of my own pride
My God
I need a hope I can't deny
In the end I'm realizing I was never meant
to fight on my own
Every little thing that I've known is every
thing I need to let go
You're so much bigger than the world I've
made
So I surrender my soul
I'm reaching out for your hope
I lay my weapons down
I'm ready for you now.
Bring me out
come and find me in the dark now
Everyday by myself I'm breaking down
I don't wanna fight alone anymore
Bring me out
from the prison of my own pride
My God
I need a hope I can't deny
In the end I'm realizing I was never meant to fight on my own
I don't wanna be incomplete
I remember what you said to me
I don't have to fight alone
Bring me out
come and find me in the dark now
Everyday by myself I'm breaking down
I don't wanna fight alone anymore
Bring me out
from the prison of my own pride
My God
I need a hope I can't deny
In the end I'm realizing I was never meant to fight on my own